ALthoug the story os this film is fictious , The events depicted involving psychic
phenomena are not only very much within the bounds of possibility , but could well be true .
Dr. Barrett ?
My people tell me
you 're among the best five in your field .
Your fee will be libras 100,000 .
Your assignment : to establish the facts .
Regarding what ?
survival after death .
You want me
To Let me know if it 's factual .
What would convince you either way ?
Give me the facts .
Where can I find these facts ? I 'm a physiscist ...
In 20 years of study psicologia
You 'LL find them in the only place I Know on Earth
where survival hasn 't yet been refuted .
The BeLasco House .
hell House ?
hell House .
The BeLascos sealed it up after what happened .
20 years ago . They need money now .
I 've bought the place .
Can you be there Monday ?
well , can you ?
Yes .
There 'LL be two others .
florence Tanner- -
Tanner ? But she 's a mental medium .
Yes . I want that approach employed , too .
She 's practically a child .
My people tell me
she 's the best in her field , too .
And the other one ?
The only survivor from the Last attempt .
Fischer ?
I expect an answer within a week .
A week ?
Take it or Leave it .
I have a List of all phenomena
recorded at the BeLasco House ,
restoration of electricity ,
transportation of your equipment .
Is that it ?
No . There 's a partially constructed machine .
How Long before it 's complete ?
Depends on how many electronics experts you use .
How soon will you need it ?
Wednesday .
Good day .
It would be better if you didn 't come .
But I always come with you .
I don 't want to be Left alone .
I want to be there
when you prove your new theory .
Isn 't it just another so-caLLed haunted house ?
It 's the Mount Everest of haunted houses .
There were two attempts to investigate it .
Both were disasters . Eight people died .
Fischer was the only survivor .
He crawled out a mental wreck .
These are the house keys .
Your Luggage and equipment
has already been installed .
electricity 's on . Your rooms are ready .
There 's a full Larder .
I 'LL return at 5 : 00 on the 2 4th .
Look at the windows .
He had them bricked up so no one could see in .
Or out .
It 's hideous .
We 're not even inside yet , Miss Tanner .
I don 't have to be .
[ Trying Light Switch ]
So much for electricity .
There 's a generator ?
Yes .
My God , that smell .
The atmosphere in here .
Of this world , not the next .
This house ...
it knows we 're here .
Miss Tanner .
Sorry .
I 'LL keep my observations to myself .
Do you know where the emergency generator is ?
I hope I didn 't disturb you .
It 's just that I 'm concerned for you coming here .
Yes , I understand .
I wonder if you do .
Just how wealthy was Mr. BeLasco ?
I believe he Left millions when he died .
Died ?
If there 's anything you 'd care to tell us ...
What 's to tell ?
The house tried to kill me .
It almost succeeded .
That Leads to the cellars , Mr. Fischer ?
That 's right .
What 's through there ?
The chapel .
chapel ?
Sorry . I can 't right now .
We understand .
welcome to my house .
I 'm delighted you could come .
I 'm certain you willfind your stay most illuminating .
Think of me as your unseen host ...
Why couLdn 't Miss Tanner come in ?
Her system is attuned to psychic energy .
obviously , it 's very strong in here .
A church in hell , that sort of thing .
Why doesn 't it affect him ?
obviously , he protects himself
better than she does .
Miss Tanner .
Miss Tanner ?
I 'm sure it 's nothing .
Are you ?
Miss Tanner ?
I 'm over here .
You shouLdn 't have done that ,
Miss Tanner .
You caused us undue alarm .
I heard a voice in here .
welcome to my house .
I 'm delighted you could come .
I 'm certain you willfind your stay most illuminating .
Think of me as your unseen host .
believe that during your stay here ,
I shaLLbe with you
in spirit .
May you find the answer you seek .
It is here , I promise you .
And now , auf wiedersehen .
Auf wiedersehen .
" till we meet again . "
The record wasn 't for us .
What made the record go on ?
BeLasco said he could will people
to a particular object ,
then move among them unobserved .
I doubt that .
Do you ?
Our attention was on that a few moments ago .
How do you know he didn 't walk right by us ?
This house hasn 't Lived up to its reputation so far .
It hasn 't taken our measure yet .
Don 't consider the house the haunting force .
Quite evidently , the problem is created
by multiple surviving personalities .
I take it you don 't believe in survival , Dr. Barrett .
If you mean surviving personalities ,
you 're correct .
We will see .
Indeed we shall .
When was the house built ?
I don 't know .
Mr. Fischer ?
1 91 9 .
You seem to know a Lot about BeLasco .
would you mind sharing it with us ?
His first name was Emeric .
He was born on March 23 , 1 87 9 ,
the illegitimate son
of an American munitions maker .
What did he Look Like ?
His was a frightening visage ,
the face of a demon
that had taken on some human aspect .
Are you quoting ?
Yes , I am .
That is his second wife .
She committed suicide in this room in 1 927 .
How tall was he ?
He was 6 ' 5 " .
They called him the Roaring Giant .
What did he do
to make this house so evil , Mr. Fischer ?
Drug addiction , alcoholism ,
sadism ,
bestiality ,
mutilation ,
murder , vampirism , necrophilia , cannibalism ,
not to mention a gamut of sexual goodies .
shall I go on ?
How did it end ?
If it had ended , we would not be here .
It 's about to end , Mr. Fischer .
What happened to Mr. BeLasco ?
No one knows .
When relatives of the guests
had this house broken into in 1 929 ,
they found all 27 of them dead .
BeLasco wasn 't among them .
If no one objects ,
I 'LL try a sitting tonight .
I have no objection .
would you care to sit
in the morning , Mr. Fischer ?
I 'm not ready yet .
Spirit of Love and tenderness ,
we gather here tonight to communicate with those
who walk this house in torment .
help us to bridge
the chasm of death so faithfully
that pain is transformed into joy ,
sorrow into peace .
ALL this we ask
in the name of our Infinite Father .
Amen .
This is an evil house ,
a place of sickness .
evil !
Extremes .
Limits .
Terminations and extremities .
I don 't know .
" If thine eye offend thee ... "
Yes .
There is a young man .
Very young .
Says he must speak .
Must speak .
[ In Spirit 's Voice ] I don 't know you people .
Why are you here ?
It does no good .
Nothing changes .
Nothing .
Get out or I 'LL hurt you .
I can 't help myself .
God damn you , you filthy sons of bitches .
God damn you !
I don 't want to hurt you ,
but I must , I must .
Get out of this house before I kill you all !
[ Pounding ]
You started manifesting physical phenomena .
But I 'm not a physical medium .
You were just now .
The embryo of one .
I don 't understand .
ALL this time a mental medium ,
and now this .
The Lord certainly does move
in mysterious ways .
So does this house .
Back to normal .
Those pounding noises are a bit unnerving
the first time you hear them .
Why was Miss Tanner so disturbed by that sitting ?
Because she caused physical phenomena .
If Miss Tanner is a mental medium
and Mr. Fischer a physical medium ,
how can you be sure she created those noises , not Fischer ?
I can 't .
In fact , I 'm not at aLL sure
about Mr. Fischer or Miss Tanner .
Who is it , please ?
You want to speak to me ?
Are you the one
that warned us to get out ?
Yes , it is you , isn 't it ?
You must give me some sign .
You 're not BeLasco , are you ?
Such a pain would not be in BeLasco .
I feel your anguish .
Who are you ?
daniel ?
daniel BeLasco .
Very clever .
If you 're that clever ,
why are you still a prisoner in this house ?
[ Weeping ]
Good morning .
You slept well ?
Fine . And you ?
Yes , very well , thank you .
I think I have a partial answer
to the haunting , Doctor .
That young man that warned us during the sitting
came to my room Last night .
BeLasco 's son .
Yes .
daniel BeLasco .
He 's very young and frightened .
Because he 's so frightened ,
he 's very hostile .
If I convince him to move on ,
the haunting force will be eliminated .
Do so by all means .
I 'd Like to suggest another sitting ,
under scientific conditions this time .
Miss Tanner in apparent trance .
pulse rate 85 , respiration 1 5 .
Four electric contacts maintained .
No change in temperature . Steady at 73.2 .
Dynamometer reading decreased to 1 823 now .
Temperature Lowering .
Now it 's 69.6 degrees .
pulse rate 94.5 and rising .
Temperature drop now 1 2.3 degrees .
Dynamometer reading reduced to 1 77 9 .
Pressurometer negative .
electric contacts still maintained .
Rate of breath increasing .
50 .
57 .
60 .
Rising steadily .
[ clicking ]
Infrared rays broken . Cameras activated .
Evidence of electromagnetic radiation commencing .
Medium 's respiration 21 0 .
Dynamometer 1 460 .
Temperature ...
[ clicking ]
Evidence of ozone in the air .
EctopLasm forming .
Separate filaments exuding from fingertips of both hands
uniting to form two separate strands .
Two strands moving toward each other .
EctopLasmic stalk through net , moving toward table .
Leave a sample , please .
Leave a sample in the jar .
Aah !
hold it .
She 's aLL right .
Miss Tanner coming out of trance .
Premature retraction of ectoplasm
causing brief systemic shock .
conclusion of sitting , 2 : 48 P.M.
I spoiled your sitting , didn 't I ?
Not at aLL .
I couLdn 't be more satisfied .
Take a Look .
What is it ?
A specimen of that teLepLasm prepared in water .
What the spiritualists refer to as ectoplasm
is derived almost entirely from the medium 's body ,
the remainder being admixtures
from the air , the medium 's costume ,
fibrous remains , dust particles .
But the bulk is organic Living matter ,
an organic externaLization of thought- -
Mind reduced to matter .
She made that figure from herself ?
I was visited by BeLasco 's son
again this afternoon .
Were you ?
will it never end ?
will what never end ?
Your attitude of doubt and distrust .
Why should mediums be expected to perform
only under conditions that science dictates ?
We 're not machines !
I 'm not a medium for fun .
Do you think- -
I believe mediumship
is God 's manifestation in man .
" When I speak to thee , I wiLL open thy mouth
" and thou shalt say unto thee ,
thus saith the Lord . "
There 's nothing in the bible
that doesn 't occur today ,
be it sights or sounds ,
coming through closed doors ,
Levitations ,
or the speaking in tongues !
Miss Tanner ,
I don 't know what this is about .
Aah !
Oh !
No !
Mr. Fischer , you must go .
What do you mean ?
You know .
You 're the physical medium .
You 're being used . You 're not in control .
You 've got to Leave !
Trying to get rid of us both now ?
What do you mean ?
Doctor , what do you mean ?
I would have thought that was obvious .
What is he saying ? That I 'm responsible ?
You 're the one who should Leave this house .
You 're the one who 's being used ,
not me .
Do we have to stay ?
This is important to me .
What if you 're hurt again ?
I won 't be . I 'LL see to it !
surely you noticed how it aLL ended
with a word from her ,
how I was the only one who was attacked .
I angered her .
You think Miss Tanner was responsible ?
Not unassisted .
There 's a Lot of power in this house , Ann .
She was the one who used it , though .
Directed it at me .
I made a mistake .
I accepted quiet , polite behavior toward me
at face value .
You can 't do that with a medium .
You never know what 's underneath .
[ knock On Door ]
May I speak to you ?
I 'LL only be a moment .
Were you badly hurt ?
I 'LL manage .
I know what happened now , Doctor .
It was BeLasco 's son .
He 's trying to separate us .
We 're Less of a challenge that way .
I 'LL sit for you tomorrow .
There 'LL be no further sittings .
You can 't stop them now !
I 'm doing so .
You don 't think I did all that ?
I know it !
PLease . I 'm in considerable pain .
Doctor , I am not responsible .
It was BeLasco 's son .
Miss Tanner !
There is no such person .
You 're wrong .
lionel ?
[ Moaning ]
lionel !
Where are you going now ?
To Look for something .
Proof that BeLasco 's son existed ?
I 'm sorry if I insulted you before .
Mrs. Barrett .
Mrs. Barrett !
You ...
me ...
that girl ...
lionel ...
aLL together ...
naked ...
drunk ...
cLutching ...
sweating ...
biting ...
Aah !
You ...
You were walking in your sleep .
Mrs. Barrett .
[ Voices ]
daniel , I 've found you .
[ Chain rattles ]
Aah !
What is it ? What happened ?
daniel BeLasco . I 've found him .
well , I 'm not imagining it .
He attacked me .
Did I imagine this ?
He 's in there behind the wall .
" Ashes to ashes , dust to dust .
" O Lord , we beseech Thee
" mercifully to receive
" the prayers of Thy people
" and grant that they may know
that which they ought to do . "
florence .
Is that you ?
help me , florence .
Why ? Why ?
You should have gone on .
You 're my only hope .
Your body was buried .
I prayed for you .
PLease , florence .
No . You have to go .
You 've been given your release .
You are my only hope .
You must go on .
You are my only hope , florence .
What does he want ?
No . I can 't .
PLease , florence .
No !
[ Door Opens ]
[ Hiss ]
What in the name of God ?
[ Cat Screeches ]
Aah !
[ Screech ]
Oh !
Aah !
[ Hiss ]
Aah ! Aah !
[ Screech ]
florence .
[ Whimpering ]
Doctor .
Miss Tanner 's been hurt again .
Where is she ?
She 's in her room .
She 's been bitten and scratched .
How did it happen ?
I don 't know . A cat , I think .
A cat ?
It was possessed by daniel BeLasco .
would you Like me to examine you ?
This will prevent infection .
I 'm all right .
I know you think- -
It doesn 't matter what I think .
What matters is your being mauled .
I 'm all right .
I wonder if that is so .
ShouLdn 't you Leave ?
No ! I 'm not Leaving now .
I 'd be falling in my duty
if I didn 't warn you to Leave .
I don 't want you
to be another victim of hell House .
He 's right , you know . You should Leave .
You 're being torn to pieces .
You don 't think I 'm doing this to myself ?
Of course I don 't .
You say it 's daniel BeLasco ,
but what if you 're wrong ?
What if you 're being fooled ?
fooled ?
daniel BeLasco does exist .
We found his body .
We Laid him to rest . Why is he not at rest ?
I think I know .
controlled multiple haunting .
Something unique in haunted houses .
A surviving will so powerful
that he can use that power to dominate
all other surviving sources .
You mean Emeric BeLasco ?
He 's the one that 's kept me from the chapel .
He made it seem as if daniel possessed the cat .
He 's the one that 's keeping daniel 's soul imprisoned here .
He 's Like a general with his army- -
Never entering the battle ,
but always controlling it .
Just what have you been doing ,
Mr. Fischer ?
Hmm ?
Have you been drinking ?
I don 't think that 's any of your business ,
although I do think it 's a very good idea .
Come on .
No .
You come on .
Mrs. Barrett .
Yes ... Ben ?
You should not Leave your husband alone .
Oh , I think he 's aLL right .
He 's sleeping .
Mrs. Barrett , you must go back upstairs .
Did you know that this was where it aLL happened ?
Where all what happened ?
ALL that debauchery and vice .
Right here .
Right around this very table .
Mrs. Barrett ,
you don 't know what you 're saying .
Oh , yes , I do .
I know exactly what I 'm saying ,
Mr. Fischer .
Mr. B.F. Fischer .
Mrs. Barrett , it 's this house .
It 's making you- -
This house isn 't doing anything .
I 'm doing it .
Touch me ,
or I 'LL find somebody who will !
No !
Oh .
I know you won 't forgive me ... now .
I know what I did .
I 'd give anything to undo it .
I just don 't know why I went down those stairs .
I knew what I was doing .
I knew , but at the same time ...
I 'm not asking you to forgive me ,
but please , please don 't hate me .
I need you .
I Love you .
I just don 't understand what 's happening to me .
I just don 't understand .
It 's aLL right .
It 'LL pass after we 've Left this house .
I Love you , too .
Doctor , I think your wife is in danger .
Mr. Fischer .
It was not her fault .
PLease , Mr. Fischer .
This is a matter of Life and death .
She walked down here Last night .
When ?
Near midnight .
You were asleep .
So was she .
She walked in her sleep ?
Yes .
You should have told me .
No , Doctor . She should have .
The fact that she didn 't ...
I don 't think you know
what 's going on in this house .
What I think is irrelevant .
What the hell do you mean by irrelevant ?
Whatever is getting at your wife
has already gotten to Miss Tanner and to you .
You 're blocking yourself off completely .
Mr. Deutsch is wasting a third of his money .
blocking yourself off completely .
I am not blocking anything .
I 'm just not sticking my neck out
the way I did in 1 953 .
Aaah !
Aaaaaaahhh !
Uh !
Eee !
[ knock On Door ]
Ben ? I 've been think- -
Give up .
Give up ?
What 's happened ?
I thought we trusted each other .
I don 't trust anyone or anything .
Anyone who does in this house is a fool .
Something has happened .
Lots of things .
Nothing we can 't handle .
Wrong .
There is nothing in this house
that we can handle .
That 's not true .
We 've made wonderful progress .
Toward what ?
Our graves ?
daniel and the way BeLasco works .
daniel !
daniel ! daniel ! daniel !
How do you know he ever existed ?
The body .
How do you know that he isn 't
a figment of your imagination ?
How do you know his personality
isn 't what you made of it ?
I know I 'm right .
We knew we were right in 1 953 .
Grace Lauter , a successful medium for- -
For 20 years .
She jumped off the balcony ,
and she shattered both her Legs .
Dr. Graham ...
physicist .
He crawled out of this house ...
to die .
Professor Rand ,
head of the chemistry department
at the University of Oxford ...
paraLyzed .
Professor FenLey ...
psychic investigator ...
crippLed and insane to this day .
Yes , uh ...
You 're right .
I am obstructing .
You 're quite right .
I 'm shut off .
I am going to stay shut off
until I am far away from this place .
I am going to collect my libras1 00,000 ,
and I am never going to come
within 1 , 000 miles of this house
for as Long as I Live ,
and I suggest you do the same .
Ben .
[ Water Running ]
Huh !
Aah !
Can I do anything to help ?
I 'm afraid not .
It 's just too complicated .
Thanks all the same .
What 's it going to do , lionel ?
You 've heard me talk
about a power in this house .
It 's a real power , Ann ,
a field of measurable energy .
Energy that can be reversed .
That 's what I 'm going to do .
By this time tomorrow ,
hell House will be de-energized .
You 'LL see .
[ clapping ]
That pile of junk you have
isn 't going to do a thing .
Get her out of here !
You haven 't a chance .
Have you ?
Yes . I know the score .
You do not fight this house !
hell House doesn 't mind a guest .
What it doesn 't Like is people who attack it .
BeLasco doesn 't Like it .
His people will fight back ,
and they 'LL kill you .
Leave that machine alone .
When Sunday comes ,
tell old Deutsch anything and bank the money .
If you try anything else ,
you will be a dead man .
He won 't Listen , will he ?
I was the only one
to get out of here alive and sane in 1 953 .
I wiLL be the only one to make it out this time .
He 's wrong .
I told you before ,
what florence Tanner believes is wrong .
I 'm telling you now
that Fischer is equally wrong .
Tomorrow , it will be proved .
florence .
help me .
PLease .
[ Moaning ]
Love me .
[ Roaring And Shrieking ]
florence .
Don 't go , florence . help me .
florence , help me .
help me , florence .
[ Voices Echoing ]
florence .
daniel , you must understand .
What you ask is impossible .
I can 't .
I believe in you .
I 've opened my heart to you .
PLease , help me .
PLease , Love me .
florence .
Love me .
No .
PLease , help me .
florence .
PLease ...
help me .
Love me .
Dear God ...
reach down Your hand
and give me Your protection .
help me this night to bring to Your care
the tortured soul of daniel BeLasco .
[ Voices ]
I give you now the Love you 've never known .
I give it so you will gain strength
to Leave this house .
I Love you .
And I Love you .
With Love , please , with Love .
Hah !
Oh .
Ah .
florence .
Aaahh !
Aaaaahhh !
Mm hm hm !
florence .
How Long have you been here ?
ALL night .
There ?
Stupid .
You could have slept with me .
Who put on my nightdress ?
Mrs. Barrett .
Why didn 't you do it ?
My God . He 's inside me .
He Lied to me .
He said it was the only way .
But he 's inside me !
I can feel him
just waiting in there to take over .
It will be all right .
I wiLL take you out of here .
He won 't Let me go .
He can 't stop you .
He can .
He can 't stop me .
[ In Spirit 's Voice ] Who do you think you are ,
you bastard ?
You might have been hot stuff before ,
but now you 're shit !
Dear God , help me .
I 'm taking her away .
How are you , Miss Tanner ?
I 'm all right .
You needn 't come back , Mr. Fischer .
The house will be clear .
clear ?
How ?
There isn 't time for explanation .
Yes , there is .
florence .
I am not Leaving until I know .
ALL right .
The body emits a form of energy
invisible to the human eye .
This energy can be expanded
far beyond the body ,
where it can create
mechanical , chemical , physical effects ,
sounds , moving objects Like we 've experieced .
The energy I talk about
is a field of electromagnetic radiation .
E.M.R.
exactly .
ALL Living organisms emit this energy .
Such power must saturate its environment .
Is it any wonder
that hell House is the way it is ?
Consider the mental and physical energy
which is being poured into its interior .
The house is a giant battery ,
the residual energy of which
must be tapped .
We survive with this energy after death .
No , Miss Tanner .
This residue has nothing to do
with surviving personalities .
The spirit of Emeric BeLasco
does not prowl this house .
Neither does his son
or any other entities
that you believe yourself to be in contact with .
There is one thing
and one thing only in this house- -
mindless , directionless power .
You 're wrong , Dr. Barrett .
You cannot destroy a spirit .
ALL you will do is send it to another hell .
No , Miss Tanner .
I 'm right .
My machine will fill the house
with a massive countercharge
of electromagnetic radiation ,
opposing the polarity of the atmosphere ,
reversing , and dissipating it .
And hell House will be exorcised .
I see .
well , there 's nothing else to do then .
Barrett .
Ah !
Thank God she didn 't know what to smash .
I should be flattered .
Her attack on the reverser
was her ultimate tribute .
She knows I 'm right .
There was nothing else to do .
That 's what she said .
She had to destroy my beliefs
before they destroyed hers .
daniel ?
[ Roaring Noise ]
[ Crying ]
Aah !
No !
[ Voices ]
Aah !
No !
Aaahh !
florence .
daniel , you must Leave before it 's too Late .
Soon you 'LL be sent from this hell to another .
Aah !
Where is Miss Tanner ?
She was Lying over there .
Why didn 't you watch her ?
Ah ! Oh !
florence .
You tricked me .
God help me , you tricked us all .
Ha ha ha !
Ah !
[ Humming ]
quickly .
[ Voices ]
You 'LL have to open yourself to it , Mr. Fischer .
Try , Mr. Fischer .
I guarantee there 'LL be no trouble .
well ?
He 's startled because there 's nothing to pick up .
Is it really over , lionel ?
Yes . It 's over .
Done with , finished .
I can 't believe it .
I know .
Do you mind if I say I told you so ?
What a pity Miss Tanner died
when the answer was so close .
Barrett .
Barrett , the house is clear .
It is completely clear !
And I called that machine a pile of junk .
You better go and get some rest .
I want to check my readings .
[ clicking ]
[ Beeping ]
[ CLacking ]
This is impossible .
I don 't accept this .
I do not accept this !
lionel ?
lionel .
lionel !
In here .
lionel ?
Here .
Aah !
No !
I 'm sorry .
lionel .
Oh , please get me out of here .
PLease .
I 'm not Leaving .
I 'm going back to the chapel .
No . No , you can 't .
You don 't know what it 's Like in there .
I have to .
You don 't .
There is no reason to go back there .
None .
Ann , Listen .
I have to .
It 's for florence .
It 's for your husband .
If I Leave hell House now ,
my whole Life will be a failure .
You can 't solve it .
It cannot be solved .
You 're going to die ...
Like lionel ,
Like Miss Tanner .
Then I wiLL .
It 's here .
The entire house is clear
except for this one place .
Why ?
BeLasco .
That 's what the " B " inside the circle means .
She was trying to tell us
that it was only BeLasco all along .
It isn 't mindless , directionless power .
It isn 't multiple hauntings .
It 's only one .
One entity pretending to be daniel .
One entity pretending to be many others .
That 's where the answer Lies .
But what 's the key ?
What is the key ?
Extremes and Limits .
Terminations and extremities .
Oh .
Oh , God .
Of course . That 's what she meant .
Extremes .
Limits .
Legs .
Grace Lauter 's spine and Legs shattered .
Dr. Graham crawling .
Professor Rand , paralyzed .
Professor FenLey , crippled .
florence 's Legs crushed .
Your husband 's ...
" If thine eye offend thee ... "
Oh , yes , yes , yes .
BeLasco !
Whatever you do , do not interfere .
BeLasco .
Here I am .
Destroy me if you can .
Don 't Leave the job half done .
We 're here .
I 'm here !
kill me !
That 's it .
Oh , that 's it .
TeLL me something , BeLasco .
Why didn 't you ever Leave this house
when you were alive ?
Why did you despise the sunlight ?
Was it better hiding in the shadows ?
[ Whining Noise ]
No one ...
No one could really see you then ,
could they ?
No one could find out
your secret then , could they ?
You weren 't a genius !
You were a deviate !
A sawed-off little bastard !
[ Roaring Noise ]
Your mother was a bitch !
A whore !
You were a bastard !
A funny little dried-up bastard !
You 're no genius !
You 're no Roaring Giant !
What size were you , BeLasco ?
5-foot 2 ?
1 ?
I know you weren 't even 5-foot taLL .
Aah !
Emeric BeLasco .
The Roaring Giant .
Is it clear ?
This is a special moment .
Meet Emeric BeLasco .
Your husband did have part of the answer .
florence had part of it , too .
I finally found the Last part ,
that which BeLasco 's giant ego
could not face .
He so despised his own shortness
that he cut off his Legs
and wore those instead to give himself height .
" If thine eye offend thee , pluck it out . "
Maybe he was a genius after all .
Just because a man preserves his body
doesn 't make him a genius .
It 's not his body of which I 'm speaking .
This is why your husband 's machine
could not destroy his power .
These walls are sheathed with Lead .
He built himself a fortress
to protect his spirit .
He knew what was coming years before it came .
Your husband and florence
helped us to rid this house
of BeLasco .
Let us hope that their spirits
guide him to everlasting peace .
BeLasco .
Legendas em Inglês by ( c ) dcd / Maio [ 2003 ]